I have already been giving a call for the stock market. The
target is ₹
2660 per share. They feel that there will be a
recovery in it, but
after the third quarter, they are only giving the statement.
They have increased the target to ₹2920
and they have also increased this treatment by one to five
percent. And finally, Morgan
Stanley has been giving the same rate and the
target is ₹2234. Morgan is also saying that there will be
no improvement in margins before the third quarter. Auspicious color
if the experts of which they have
maintained the call for the stock. The target will be around
₹50 for the stock and
a good skill is being seen in health and size
and this will be a drive in fact
for greeting this last inch, then the
number is the highest and here the stop whose Beckham could have gone.
Talking about Ambuja Cement,
remember the judgment in front of the calendar.
Targets have been reduced on many companies, so
Bank of America Merrill Lynch is saying that
their target will be ₹410. The rating of the bike
is Asif, in fact, has downgraded the sell rating.  The
target given is 340 versus 400.
Credit Suisse is also deep neutral with a
new target of 335. The first one was 410 and
Jefferies has maintained a hold rating
for the target of 400. So there have been some
downgrades here and the targets have
definitely been seen. NFC closed
Jhal Jhal